Guide to The Alfred C. Berol Collection of Lewis Carroll 1845-1993 MSS.057
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence, 109217
  - Subseries 1A: Correspondence from Charles L. Dodgson, 109298
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 19, 1888 (XI 159) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 701)., 1425; 109392 (Box 4, Folder 353)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 24, 1888 (XI 160) 5 x 8., 1429; 109391 (Box 4, Folder 354)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, December 24, [1889] (XI 162) 4 x 6.25 (Cohen pg. #: 771)., 1446; 109390 (Box 4, Folder 355)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 3pp [Christ, Church, Oxford], February 24, [1890], 4:35 p.m. (XI 161) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 778)., 1442; 109389 (Box 4, Folder 356)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, November 12, 1890 (XI 163) 4.5 x 7., 1432; 109388 (Box 4, Folder 357)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 13, 1891 (XI 164) 5 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 831)., 1433; 109387 (Box 4, Folder 358)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, June 30, 1891 (XI 165) 5 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 848)., 1436; 109386 (Box 4, Folder 359)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, illus, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 2, 1893 (XI 166) 5 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 944)., 1439; 109385 (Box 4, Folder 360)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, Professor J.A. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, June 8, 1881 (X 132) With envelope. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 432)., 1449; 109384 (Box 4, Folder 361)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 10, 1886 (X 133) 4.5 x 7., 1450; 109383 (Box 4, Folder 362)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 12, 1889 (X 134) 7 x 4.5 (Cohen pg. #: 738)., 1453; 109382 (Box 4, Folder 363)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, November 11, 1892 (X 136) 5.5 x 7., 1456; 109381 (Box 4, Folder 364)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, March 25, 1893 (X 138)See manuscripts. Possibly refers to manuscript to Stewart dated March 23, 1893. 3.75 x 6., 109380 (Box 4, Folder 365)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, February 10, 1894 (X 139) With envelope. 8.5 x 8.5., 1458; 109379 (Box 4, Folder 366)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, March 8, 1894 (X 140) With envelope. 3.5 x 5.25., 1459; 109378 (Box 4, Folder 367)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 1pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 12, 1894 (X 141) With AN, 1p dated "12/3/94.". 5.75 x 8.75., 1460; 109377 (Box 4, Folder 368)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. Als, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, March 22, 1894 (X 142) 4.5 x 7., 1463; 109376 (Box 4, Folder 369)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. Als, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, December 14, 1897 (X 143) With envelope. 4.25 x 7., 1464; 109375 (Box 4, Folder 370)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 1p [n.p., n.d.] (X 135) With envelope. 4 x 6.25., undated; 1465; 109374 (Box 4, Folder 371)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Ellen Als, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, June 12, 1897. 7 x 9., 1466; 109373 (Box 4, Folder 372)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Florence Als, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, December 22, [1881] (574) 5.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 449)., 1469; 109372 (Box 4, Folder 373)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Lewis Als, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, May 8, 1879 (573) 7 x 9., 1472; 109371 (Box 4, Folder 374)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, November 14, 1882 With envelope. 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 470)., 1476; 109370 (Box 4, Folder 375)
    - Dodgson, Charles to Terry, Marion "Lewis Carroll"s Letters to Marion Terry, 1869-1897" Red Leather Album with 10 letters.., 109369 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 3pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, August 2, 1869 (V 84) With envelope. Pasted in red leather album of letters. 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 133)., 1481; 109368 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, December 24, 1878 (V 85) Pasted in red leather album of letters. 6.25 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 322)., 1485; 109367 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 1p [n.p.] January 17, 1879 (V 86)Originally Enclosed with Lanrick game pasted on next page of album. Pasted in red leather album of letters. 6.25 x 7.75., 1490; 109366 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 2, 1878 (V 87) Pasted in red leather album of letters. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 312)., 1493; 109365 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 8, 1881 (V 88) Pasted in red leather album of letters. 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 407)., 1499; 109364 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion AD, illus [n.p., n.d.] (V 89) With envelope. Pasted in red leather album of letters. 5 x 8., undated; 1502; 109363 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 14, 1887 (V 90) Pasted in red leather album of letters. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 663)., 1503; 109362 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 3, 1892 (V 91) Pasted in red leather album of letters. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 897)., 1507; 109361 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, November 18, 1895 (V 92) Pasted in red leather album of letters. 3.5 x 5.25 (Cohen pg. #: 1077)., 1512; 109360 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, October 26, 1897 (V 93) With envelope. Pasted in red leather album of letters. 3.5 x 5.25., 1515; 109359 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Tidy, Kathleen ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 30, 1861 (XIX 450) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 49)., 1518; 109358 (Box 4, Folder 377)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Todd, W.E. ACs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 9, 1882 (XIX 476) 3 x 4.75., 1523; 109357 (Box 4, Folder 378)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Todd, Mrs. W.E. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, April 4, 1876 (XIX 477) With envelope.. 5.25 x 6.75., 1526; 109356 (Box 4, Folder 379)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Todd, Mrs. W.E. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 18, 1880 (XIX 478) With envelope.. 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 379)., 1527; 109355 (Box 4, Folder 380)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Todd, Mrs. W.E. ALs, 4pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, Jan 5, 1884 (XIX 479) 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 523)., 1530; 109354 (Box 4, Folder 381)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Vibert, Janet ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, May 28, 1896 (329) 5.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1091)., 1535; 109353 (Box 4, Folder 382)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Walters, H.L.M. ALs, 2pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 5, 1898 (XIX 564) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 1154)., 1539; 109352 (Box 4, Folder 383)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, January 23, 1888 (XIX 511) 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 692)., 1542; 109351 (Box 4, Folder 384)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 26, 1888 (XIX 512) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 716)., 1545; 109350 (Box 4, Folder 385)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, January 10, 1892 (XIX 541) 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 884)., 1548; 109349 (Box 4, Folder 386)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, January 15, 1892 (XIX 516) With envelope. Envelope is incorrectly numbered XIX 511. 5.5 x 7., 1552; 109348 (Box 4, Folder 387)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, October 3, 1895 (XIX 513) With envelope. 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1074)., 1553; 109347 (Box 4, Folder 388)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, October 6, 1895 (XIX 514) With envelope. 4.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1074)., 1556; 109346 (Box 4, Folder 389)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, October 8, 1895 (XIX 515) 4.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1075)., 1559; 109345 (Box 4, Folder 390)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, January 27, 1896 (XIX 542) 4.25 x 7., 1562; 109344 (Box 4, Folder 391)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Webb, Miss ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, Monday, 6:30, [February 20, 1888] (XIX 520) 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 697)., 1565; 109343 (Box 4, Folder 392)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Webb, Miss ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 26, 1888 (XIX 521) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 702)., 1569; 109342 (Box 4, Folder 393)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Webb, Miss ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 29, 1888 (XIX 522) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 702)., 1572; 109341 (Box 4, Folder 394)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Whatford, Jack Henry ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 24, 1892 (XIX 548) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 929)., 1575; 109340 (Box 4, Folder 395)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 7, 1877 (XII 167) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 269)., 1579; 109339 (Box 5, Folder 396)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 8, 1885 (XII 168) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 563)., 1583; 109338 (Box 5, Folder 397)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, December 16, 1885 (XII 169) With envelope. 6 x 7.5 (Cohen pg. #: 612)., 1587; 109337 (Box 5, Folder 398)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, January 29, 1886 (XII 170) With envelope. 5.25 x 6.5 (Cohen pg. #: 618)., 1591; 109336 (Box 5, Folder 399)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 5, 1886 (XII 171) 5.25 x 6.5., 1592; 109335 (Box 5, Folder 400)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 18, 1886 (XII 172) With envelope. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 621)., 1595; 109334 (Box 5, Folder 401)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, March 29, 1886 (XII 173) 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 629)., 1599; 109333 (Box 5, Folder 402)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, June 1, 1886 (XII 174) With envelope.. 5.25 x 6.75., 1600; 109332 (Box 5, Folder 403)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 21, 1887 (XII 175) With envelope. 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 666)., 1604; 109331 (Box 5, Folder 404)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 6, 1889 (XII 176) With envelope. 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 728)., 1607; 109330 (Box 5, Folder 405)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 8, 1889 (XII 177) With envelope. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 728)., 1611; 109329 (Box 5, Folder 406)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, May 24, 1889 (XII 178) 5.5 x 7., 1614; 109328 (Box 5, Folder 407)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, May 28, 1889 (XII 179) 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 741)., 1615; 109327 (Box 5, Folder 408)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 30, 1889 (XII 180). 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 765)., 1618; 109326 (Box 5, Folder 409)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, December 5, 1890 (XII 181) 4.5 x 7., 1623; 109325 (Box 5, Folder 410)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, December 6, 1890 (XII 182) Docketed on verso. 6 x 3.75., 1624; 109324 (Box 5, Folder 411)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, June 15, 1891 (XII 183) With envelope. 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 846)., 1627; 109323 (Box 5, Folder 412)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 26, 1891 (XII 184) With envelope.. 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 874)., 1631; 109322 (Box 5, Folder 413)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, December 25, 1891 (XII 185) With envelope. 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 877)., 1635; 109321 (Box 5, Folder 414)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 4, 1892 (XII 186) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 891)., 1639; 109320 (Box 5, Folder 415)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Guildford, December 22, 1893 (XII 187) 4.5 x 7., 1644; 109319 (Box 5, Folder 416)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, July 3, 1894 (XII 188) With envelope. 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1028)., 1645; 109318 (Box 5, Folder 417)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, October 22, 1895 (XII 190) 4.5 x 7., 1648; 109317 (Box 5, Folder 418)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, March 6, 1897 (XII 191) 3.75 x 6., 1649; 109316 (Box 5, Folder 419)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 4, 1898 (XII 193) 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1154)., 1652; 109315 (Box 5, Folder 420)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, Wednesday, 10 a.m. [n.d.] (XII 192) With envelope.. 3.5 x 5.25., undated; 1578; 109314 (Box 5, Folder 421)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Menella ALs, 3pp Grosvenor House, 44 Grand Parade, Eastbourne, July 14, 1877 (XIX 474) Possibly refers to Poem Nella"s Song. See Manuscripts. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 279)., 0592; 109313 (Box 5, Folder 422)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Menella ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 20, 1886 (XIX 473) Possibly refers to Poem Nella"s Song. See Manuscripts. 6 x 4 (Cohen pg. #: 633)., 0596; 109312 (Box 5, Folder 423)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, William E. ALs, 11pp Christ Church, Oxford, May 11, 1859 (336) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 35)., 1675; 109311 (Box 5, Folder 424)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, William M. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, October 30, 1876 (XIX 466) 6 x 7.75., 1653; 109310 (Box 5, Folder 425)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, William M. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 23, 1880 (XIX 467) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 393)., 1657; 109309 (Box 5, Folder 426)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, William M. ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 25, 1880 (XIX 468) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 394)., 1661; 109308 (Box 5, Folder 427)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, William M. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, June 7, 1881 (XIX 469) 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 431)., 1666; 109307 (Box 5, Folder 428)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, William M. ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 10, 1885 (XIX 470) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 602)., 1670; 109306 (Box 5, Folder 429)
    - Dodgson, Charles to Wilcox, Mrs. W.E. Envelope (1) (XII 189)., undated; 109305 (Box 5, Folder 430)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Yonge, Charlotte ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, December 8, 1877 (XIX 475) 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 290)., 1687; 109304 (Box 5, Folder 431)
    - Dodgson, Charles To "Dolly" [?] PLs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, April 5, 1882 No number. Circular letter re: an edition of Shakespeare for girls. 7 x 9, 1690; 109303 (Box 5, Folder 432)
    - Dodgson, Charles To "The Editor of the Standard" ALs, 1p [n.p.] December 10, 1893 (I 28) 9 x 5.5, 1692; 109302 (Box 5, Folder 433)
    - Dodgson, Charles To "Professor" ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, January 30, [n.y.] (XIX 539) 5.25 x 3.5, undated; 1693; 109301 (Box 5, Folder 434)
    - Dodgson, Charles To "Sir" ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 17, 1894 Detailed discussions of math and logic. 11.75 x 8.75, 1696; 109300 (Box 5, Folder 435)
    - Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1pp To "Sir" 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 17, 1894 Detailed discussions of math and logic. 11.75 x 8.75, 1698; 109299 (Box 5, Folder 436)
  - Subseries 1B: Correspondence to Charles L. Dodgson, 109234
    - Beach, Sir Michael Hicks to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Board of Trade, Whitehall Gardens, May 28, 1892 (XV 274) Marked "78507". 7.25 x 9.5, 2073; 109297 (Box 5, Folder 437)
    - Darwin, G.H. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Nice, January 30, 1885 (XV 250) 6.5 x 8.25, 2077; 109296 (Box 5, Folder 438)
    - du Maurier, George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp 91 Great Russell Street, December 23, [n.y.] (XV 240) 7 x 9, [1867]; 2081; 109295 (Box 5, Folder 439)
    - Frost, Arthur Burdett to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 4pp n.p., May 5, 1881 (XV 251) Marked "36802" 8 x 10, 2085; 109294 (Box 5, Folder 440)
    - Furniss, Harry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp 23 St. Edmund"s Terrace, Regent"s Park, March 2, 1885 (XV 275)Marked "49533". 7 x 9, 2090; 109293 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Furniss, Harry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 7pp 23 St. Edmund"s Terrace, Regent"s Park, April 8, 1885 (XV 276) Marked "49958". 7 x 9, 2094; 109292 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Furniss, Harry to Dodgson, Charles ANs, 2pp 23 St. Edmund"s Terrace, Regent"s Park, June 13, 1885 (XV 277). 7 x 9, 2101; 109291 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Furniss, Harry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, illus, 4pp Kent, August 23, 1886 (XV 278) Marked "54696". 7 x 9, 2104; 109290 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Furniss, Harry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, illus, 8pp 23 St. Edmund"s Terrace, Regent"s Park, October 10, 1889 (XV 279) Marked "67067". 8 x 10, 2109; 109289 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Furniss, Harry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 23 St. Edmund"s Terrace, Regent"s Park, November 8, n.y. (XV 280)Marked "84666". 8 x 10, undated; 2118; 109288 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Holman-Hunt, W. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp [T]or Villa, Cam[p]den Hill, Kensington W., July 24, 186[1] (XV 234) 5.5 x 7, 2119; 109287 (Box 5, Folder 442)
    - Holman-Hunt, W. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp 3 Wilton Terrace, Campden Hill W., February 7, 1873 (XV 235) Marked "14963". 7 x 9, 2123; 109286 (Box 5, Folder 442)
    - Holman-Hunt, W. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Draycott Lodge, Fulham, June 26, 1895 (XV 236)Marked "90389". 7 x 8.75, 2126; 109285 (Box 5, Folder 442)
    - Prince Leopold to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 4pp Claremont, Esher, December 22, 1889 (XV 252) Marked "68703". 7 x 9, 2130; 109284 (Box 5, Folder 443)
    - Prince Leopold to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp [n.p.] Feb 2, 1876 (XV 253). 7 x 9, 2135; 109283 (Box 5, Folder 443)
    - Liddell, H.G. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, Christ Church, Oxford, November 6, 1890 (XV 288) Marked "72524". 5.25 x 3.25, 2139; 109282 (Box 5, Folder 444)
    - Liddell, H.G. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, November 7, 1890 (XV 287) Numbered "72542". 5.25 x 3.25, 2140; 109281 (Box 5, Folder 444)
    - Liddell, H.G. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, November 27, 1890 (XV 290)Marked "72713" 6 x 4, 2141; 109280 (Box 5, Folder 444)
    - Liddell, H.G. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, March 9, 1891 (XV 289) Marked "73737". 6 x 4, 2142; 109279 (Box 5, Folder 444)
    - Liddell, H.G. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Christ Church, 5 p.m. [n.d.] (XV 291) 6 x 4, [1870]; 2143; 109278 (Box 5, Folder 444)
    - Millais, J.E. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 7 Cromwell Place, South Kensington, September 26, 1864 (XV 241). 7 x 4.5, 2144; 109277 (Box 5, Folder 445)
    - Millais, J.E. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 7 Cromwell Place, South Kensington, December 14, [1865] (XV 242). 7 x 4.5, 2145; 109276 (Box 5, Folder 445)
    - Millais, J.E. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp [n.p.] September 2, 1886 (XV 243). 6 x 3.75, 2146; 109275 (Box 5, Folder 445)
    - Millais, J.E to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 7 Cromwell Place, South Kensington, July 9, 1870 (XV 244). 5.25 x 3.5, 2149; 109274 (Box 5, Folder 445)
    - Millais, J.E. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp 7 Cromwell Place, South Kensington, [July 25, n.d.] (XV 245) 5.25 x 3.5, undated; 2150; 109273 (Box 5, Folder 445)
    - Patmore, Coventry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp Hastings, March 7, 1890 (XV 281) Marked "69490". 7 x 4.5, 2153; 109272 (Box 5, Folder 446)
    - Patmore, Coventry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Hastings, June 12, 1891 (XV 282) Marked "74597". 8 x 5, 2154; 109271 (Box 5, Folder 446)
    - Reed, B. German to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp The Old Ship Hotel, Brighton, February 2, 187[3] (XV 273) Marked "14935". 7 x 4.5, 2155; 109270 (Box 5, Folder 447)
    - Reed, B. German to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 4pp [Garrick Club], June 5, 1873 (XV 272) Marked "15726". 7 x 9, 2158; 109269 (Box 5, Folder 447)
    - Rossetti, Christina to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp 30 Torrington Square, London, [n.d.] (XV 232) 7 x 4.5, [1878]; 2163; 109268 (Box 5, Folder 448)
    - Rossetti, Dante Gabriel to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 4pp 16 Cheyne Walk, Chelsea, December 21, 1863 (XV 238) 7 x 9, 2165; 109267 (Box 5, Folder 449)
    - Ruskin, John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Corpus Christi College, Oxford [n.d.] (XV 246). 7 x 4.5, undated; 2170; 109266 (Box 5, Folder 450)
    - Ruskin, John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp November 23, [n.y.] (XV 247) Marked "21019". 7 x 9, undated; 2171; 109265 (Box 5, Folder 450)
    - Ruskin, John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Brantwood, Coniston, Lancashire, [n.d.] (XV 248) Marked "43152". 7 x 4.5, undated; 2174; 109264 (Box 5, Folder 450)
    - Ruskin, John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Brantwood, Coniston, Lancashire [n.d.] (XV 249) Marked "45395". 7 x 9, undated; 2175; 109263 (Box 5, Folder 450)
    - Salisbury, Lady Georgina to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Hatfield, August 9, [n.y.] (XV 259) Marked "27200". 7 x 9, 1878; 2176; 109262 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lady Georgina to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Hatfield House, Hatfield, Herts., [n.d.] (XV 260) Marked "5195". 7 x 4.5, [1870]; 2180; 109261 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lady Georgina to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Hatfield House, Hatfield, Herts., [n.d.] (XV 261) Marked "25936". 7 x 4.5, [1877]; 2181; 109260 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp 20 Arlington Street, S.W., May 21, [1881] (XV 262)Marked "36835". 7 x 9, 2182; 109259 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Hatfield House, Hatfield, Herts., Jan 31, 188[3] (XV 263) Marked " 38701". 7 x 9, 2186; 109258 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp 20 Arlington Street, S.W., [1884] (XV 264) Marked 7 x 4.5, 2190; 109257 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 20 Arlington Street, S.W., July [4], [1884] (XV 265) Marked "47465". 7 x 4.5, 2193; 109256 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 20 Arlington Street, S.W., November 3, [1884] (XV 266) Marked "48430". 7 x 4.5, 2196; 109255 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 20 Arlington Street, S.W., March 10, [1888] (XV 268)Marked "60899". 7 x 9, 2197; 109254 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Hatfield House, Hatfield, Herts., August 31, [1895] (XV 270) Marked "90859". 7 x 9, 2198; 109253 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Chalet Cecil, Puys pres Dieppe, September 6, 1895 (XV 271) Marked "90918". 7 x 4.5, 2202; 109252 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lady Georgina to Dodgson, Charles ALs, Hatfield House, Hatfield, Herts., April 20, [n.y.] (XV 267). 7 x 9, [1886]; 2206; 109251 (Box 5, Folder 451)